PURVANSHI SINGH

purvanshi.singh@ucdconnect.ie | +353 897 429 499 | Dublin | linkedin.com/in/purvanshi-singh

SUMMARY

Masters in Management student having 2 years of consulting experience. Skilled in strategising and implementing projects affecting key metrics around improving HR operations, performance management, staffing, employee development and organisational development for prestigious law firms.

EDUCATION

MSc in Management

Sep 2022 - Aug 2023

UCD Michael Smurfit Graduate Business School, Ireland

- *Key Modules:* Human Resource Management, Economics and Markets, Global Strategic Management, Corporate Social Responsibility
- Societies: Global Leadership Programme, Commerce and Economics Society, Kevin Barry Cumann UCD, Investors & Entrepreneurs Society
- Key Activities: Proudly Made in Africa Project, GLP leadership webinars/seminars group

B.A. L.LB (Hons.)

Jul 2014 - May 2019

University of Rajasthan, India

74.13%

- Key Modules: Company Law, Professional Ethics & Professional Accounting, Human Rights & Practice, Contract Law
- *Achievements:* Quarter Finalist at 3 National Moot Court Competitions, organised legal-aid camp offering free legal advice to 100+ members from underrepresented communities

EXPERIENCE

Consultant, Yellow Wire Consulting, India

Oct 2021 - Jul 2022

- Managed consulting engagements with 7+ law firms, influencing their HR Operations, Business Development and Social Media strategies.
- Designed a multi-platform hiring pipeline which successfully onboarded 50+ new recruits across 12 client firms.
- Delivered digital content strategies to improve clients' engagement and reach of authoritative legal opinions, generating over 3 million impressions online.

Practice Development Group, Bharucha & Partners, India

Jun 2021 - Oct 2021

- Delivered projects in critical growth areas for the firm, including Practice Development, HR, Technology and Organisation Policies.
- Redesigned the firm's onboarding strategy through which 20+ associates were onboarded 20% faster than in previous years.
- Increased the firm's LinkedIn following by 4500 using a social media marketing strategy around legal content, optimising for organic impressions.

Content Marketing Manager, MapUp Inc., India

Nov 2020 - April 2021

- Formulated and executed the content strategy for the English, Spanish and Portuguese markets, totaling over 1 million impressions per week.
- \bullet Launched 6 multi-lingual SEO campaigns, which pulled up the TollGuru website's ranking from #235,747 to #146,727 worldwide and #28,765 in the US.
- Delivered a customer support chatbot integrated with Zoho CRM and Sales I.Q. in the backend, serving over 100 users a day worldwide.

Legal Intern, Resurgent India Ltd., India

Jul 2019 - Nov 2019

- Consulted on the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) of 2 large and 3 mid-sized clients.
- Aided the Insolvency Resolution Profession in conducting Committee of Creditors meetings by capturing the minutes of the sessions, organising documents and managing client expectations.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Volunteering: Editor at Alexis Research (Mar 2020 Oct 2021), Legal Aid Cell (2018 2019)
- **Human Resource Functions:** Recruitment, Staffing, Organisation Policies, Change Management, Performance Management and Skill Management
- Digital & Social Media Marketing: Google Analytics, Google Trends, Ahref, LinkedIn Ads, Zoho CRM and Sales I.Q.
- Project Management: Scrum, Agile, Stakeholder Management, Risk Management
- Other: Microsoft Office and collaboration products (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, SharePoint, OneNote, OneDrive)